Okay, there we go. So welcome ladies, it's nice to see a few faces. And before
we get
going I just want to say a massive thank you to Sami because this call was Sami
's idea
and I think the time in of it is really great. And although we're going to be
like going
through it together just to give Sami all the credit for this because you've
worked really
hard on it. And you know, it's your little baby, it's all your idea. So thank
you so
much, Sami for doing that. And yeah, it's all about getting back to business
today, which
certainly is my energy, like getting back into camp. Now that this summer
holidays are
over and we can get back down to it. So let's go for it. So finally the
children are back
to school and calm is busier than ever. So it's been a really good month this
month. Getting
back into a routine can be difficult. So we want to share some ideas about how
to manage
working from home whilst balancing a busy life, another job, kids, etc. Or even
just
the struggle of trying to find motivation to work from home, which I'm sure is
hard
for us all sometimes. And Sami, do you want to go for this one?
So I wanted to just include a little bit about cyclical living, which is like
what I've been
really trying to stick to at the moment because I just think it can really work
with just
like your whole life basically. So it's working with your menstruation, I
really find that
word hard. So menstruation cycle. And if you're not obviously doing that and
you can work
with moon cycles instead, because both can have a profound like effect on moods
and like
just energy levels, like basically everything. I've started like since the kids
have been
back at school to combine that with like my eating habits because like
obviously over
the summer holidays, I just ain't drank way too much and fasting. So I'm
obsessed with
fasting at the moment. I find it an amazing health benefit, not just for losing
weight
but actually like repairs your body and your cells. And it just means that like
your mental
and your physical health can be so much better, which can be so much better for
work, for
life, for like your kids, your partner, whoever. So yeah, I just really think
that's a really
good thing to do. Even if you don't want to lose weight, just like look into it
because
it can reverse like cancer cells and stuff like that. I know you're going to
put that
in Sammy and I actually do it for my Crohn's. It's amazing isn't it? This can
help with
your structure and focus when you come in from time and setting yourself
realistic schedules
and goals. What I do is like I try and use like eating timers off come time and
work
it all around that. Which once you get into like a routine of it can be really
a really
great way to balance like work and home life. So yeah, whilst I can spend with
your family,
your friends and most importantly yourself. Okay, do you want me to go? I'll do
this one
shall I? Yeah. If you need to put in at any point and if anyone's got any
questions as
well, of course, feel free to add or to ask anything. So the phases, so these
are the
phases when we're looking at cyclical living. So there's the menstruation or
new moon depending
on what you're using. So here we use lighter fasting or maintenance mode. So
for example,
intermittent fasting with a wider eating window. So eating more often isn't it
throughout
the day. Taking time to rest, plan, set goals, write gratitude lists for the
previous cycle
and to set new goals and intentions. So we try and actually a few calls that we
've done.
We've done them alongside the new moon or the full moon haven't we? Which are
like current
side of the things that are good to do here. So there's some calls on the
website as well
which might be useful for these different phases. How do you say that word? F
olliculate phase.
I can't say cyclical or menstruation. Follicula. Follicula. Slash waxing
present. So new beginnings
and growth. A gradual transition into a fasting routine, which means starting
with intermittent
fasting and shorter fasting periods. So you're eating a little bit more often
than you would
be with menstruation. Is that right? I mean less often. Less often, yeah. So it
's a time
to get back on track and into your schedule which you've set on the new moon.
And then
ovulation/full moon. So this is the phase on where social and outgoing,
flexible fasting.
So intermittent fasting with a moderate fasting window. This is the time you're
invincible.
So plan social events, exercise and do that extra hour on cam or late night if
you feel
able to. And then the luteal phase, which is the waning present, is for self
reflection
and self care. So adjusting your fasting approach based on comfort. This is the
phase, or these
are Sami's words, where I personally like to cam or misjust mode. It's a great
PMT outlet
for me. This is just the way I try to adjust and integrate cyclical living into
my work
routine. Yeah, and that's a really good point. Even the style of coming that
you're doing
can be different at different times of the month, can't it, depending on your
jamena
and how you're feeling about yourself. And what you want to do as well, I guess
, at
different stages. And sometimes I feel like really horny between like the foll
icular phase
and the ovulation or like maybe it'd be like a little bit more so I'd be like,
oh, really
like switchy then. You know what I mean? I want them to just watch me because I
'm feeling
really horny. And then I just, that's how I work into each phase of like how I
feel
and what I want to do that day. And it seems to work quite well if you get into
the routine
of it. So, yeah. So when you're planning, you're thinking about like the amount
of work
you're going to do, how busy your schedule is, and how often you're going to be
eating
or healthy, I guess. And then repeat the cycle and continue aligning your
activities and
self-care practices with cyclical living, adapting the fasting approach as
needed.
Individual variations in menstrual cycles and fasting preferences obviously
will require
adjustments. It's important to listen to your body and make modifications based
on your
personal health preferences and goals. We do have another call, don't we? I
know it was
a while ago, so you'd have to scroll back quite a bit, but we do have a call on
cyclical
living that goes through, yeah, like all their phases. So if you're interested
in that,
that might be a good one, so have a look back on. Okay. Yeah. So working from
home provides
flexibility and convenience, but it also demands discipline and motivation to
stay on track.
Establishing a consistent schedule and maintaining focus are key to a
successful work from home
experience. It's important to remember not to burn out. It can be really easy
to get
carried away with calm and forget you might be like if you're having a really
good night
and you're working, it can be easy to like just think of another hour, another
hour and
then forget that you might feel like tired in the morning. If you're working in
that
evening, especially when you're doing well, so remember to set yourself some
limits or
just remember like maybe the next day or rest and sleep or catch up and sleep
or if you
can work in having a nap the following day. On the flip side, also after a
really successful
night on cam, it's important to still show up the following day and keep into
your schedule
and stay consistent because consistency I would say is probably one of the most
important
things of doing well. Hey, do you want to go with this once I make? So you can
elaborate
a bit. I've got my little notes. So set clear and realistic goals and visualise
. So I could
go on about visualisation for ages and you know how to do it and whatever else.
So I won't
go into it massively because I know we have loads of course where I've spoken
about this
but just have a night pad, set your goals, put them into chunks, visualise how
you're
going to do it, how you're going to work at it each day, what your goal is for
that day.
I think having an amount you want to earn each day, that kind of thing is quite
important
to do, not just be like I want to earn I know £10,000 by the end of the month,
be realistic
let's set your goals or this is what I want to earn this day and try and stick
to it.
Create a comfortable workspace. So a clean and tidy area is always better for
your mind
as well as it looks better. I think if you're sitting amongst powers that have
met for me
as well it's so distracting I just want to get up and clean. So if I'm in a
nice clean
and tidy area I'm relaxed I'm ready to just completely focus on working. Good
lighting
is really important obviously and somewhere that you're comfortable because you
could
be sitting up or in a funny position for a long time so don't try and sort of
be like
this. Be comfortable, make yourself comfortable before you start. So you know
that what kind
of space that you're going to feel comfortable in that space and if it wasn't
having black
acres there because you're sitting in the same position for ages. I think we
also have
a call on movement don't we within cam actually that's quite useful of how to
move your body
a little bit around and you know you're not just sitting in one position the
whole time.
Establish a routine that works for you. So a routine that aligns with your
natural energy
levels and work preferences. Set consistent hours and stick to them as much as
possible.
Establishing a routine really does help regulate your body and your mind making
it easier to
transition into work mode and maintain focus throughout the day and this could
be different
for everyone because some people have children, some people don't, some people
have other jobs,
some people don't, some people are morning people, some people are night time
people
but just establishing that routine and like really sticking to it I think it's
really
important. Dress for success. So although working in pyjamas can be tempting
getting dressed,
doing your hair and make up, wearing something you feel great in can
significantly improve
your mindset and it's so just like even putting your favourite perfume on you
know if you
look at yourself in the room and think oh I look good like you're just going to
smile
straight away and I think it massively improves your mindset and just feeling
like you're
actually going to work. So meditation and your mantra pre-ham routine. So spend
at least
wiping it with a little meditation before you go, before you start. One of them
that
I just use as an example is I'm open to receiving abundance and prosperity in
my life. I attract
wealth effortlessly and money flows to me in expected and unexpected ways. I am
worthy
of financial abundance and I use money to create positive impact in my life and
the lives
of others. One thing I always do is just take a few minutes to think of like
how I want
the session to go, what clients I want to attract, what will we speak about,
how the session
will be enjoyable for me, how much money I want to make, getting with my goals.
I probably
would have that sort of like as a target already and then I just sit just a
couple of minutes
and just visualise the whole like calm session and myself already in possession
of the financial
abundance that I desire. Feel the emotions associated with having that money
and trust
in the process. So the key to manifest in your dream life is to truly believe
and feel as
are you already have it visualising every aspect and practising gratitude for
everything
along the way. Share your sisterhood. So always ask if you're feeling unsure in
our amazing
WhatsApp groups, share the experiences that you've had in your session. Some
can be pretty
hilarious to be honest. Sharing your progress, challenges and goals with your
sisterhood
can provide motivation and help you stay committed. Share your successes, we're
a community
of beautiful women who love celebrating one another. Remember to also, so I've
got the
love at the end. Remember to always check in with yourself regularly about
whether the
way you're working is what's best for you. Don't be afraid of change, don't be
afraid
of trying something new. Yeah, and I think the reason I say that is because we
can get
caught up in like this set routine that we've made for ourselves and like
almost shaming
ourselves if we don't stick to it like because we preach so much about
consistency and stuff.
But that's why checking in with yourself along the way is so important, isn't
it? That's
still consistent. It's still consistent to check in and make changes and adapt.
It doesn't
have to be a rigid thing. You test it out and if it works for you, great. But
if it doesn't,
that's okay as well, isn't it? And one little point as well on the dress, the
success bit.
So I totally get what you say when you say that like I like to like, I don't
really,
I've never really camped without any makeup on. I will always put the makeup on
. I like
to like do my lips and probably a bit OTT makeup like when I'm coming because
it doesn't
look that bad on camp, does it? But sometimes I come across girls who, when we
've been at
shoots or whatever and I've just like chucked my cam on and I've been chatting
to someone
who have been like, oh, you're just going to put it on. So I think that can
also hold
you back sometimes, can't it? I think it definitely can like, of a nighttime, I
was thinking that
when I was sitting there and as I'm sitting in my fleece pajama bottoms, of a
nighttime
like I'll always come with just like, so later I've literally got like cream
fleece pyjamas
on. I'll take this cup off and just have a pink bra on and that'll be comfy. I
meant
like this is probably because I've written it so personally to me to just if I
'm not a
morning person, as you all know, so to just wake up and put my cam on, I would
fall asleep
immediately, but I'd just like to sleep. So for me, it's a personal thing, I
think like
to get up, to get dressed, to do my hair, to put a little bit of makeup on, to
wear just
something gets me motivated. Does that make sense? Yeah, no, and I completely
agree with
that. I do have a little thing that I'll always do like this and that do my
lips. But also,
just to bear in mind as well, that sometimes you don't always have to follow
this step
by step by step. If you've got like a spare hour at lunchtime and you weren't
going to
you were going to go to the gym or whatever, but you're planning to fall
through, it is
okay to just like, it's okay to just jump on in your gym kit or whatever or you
know,
so yeah, yeah, I think it's great to and it's almost a step to get into the
mindset, isn't
it to get yourself ready, but also take the opportunities where you're just
where you
can, you know, so don't don't beat yourself up about it, not being exactly
right every
time. Sometimes you can do like, so well, like you think, oh, I don't know,
like, oh,
just shove it on, but I've got just a t-shirt on or whatever, and then you end
up doing
so well, would you like, oh wow. Yeah, I actually do better at the moment in my
gym kit than
I do in the last day. I like bras a tiny, but yeah, I like the guys love the
gym kit and
I'm wearing it anyway, because I go gym every day. So yeah, that's, I mean, I
wouldn't wear
that much makeup to the gym or any, but yeah, it's good to sort of be here. I
think too
much. And remember that with any business results are never instant, so you don
't start
a business and make profit overnight, send to your goals around effort, not
money, and
the money will follow. That was one thing actually that Georgia, that was one
of Georgia's things
and I really liked that Georgia said, sent to your goals around effort, or I
don't know
if effort was the word that you use, but you know, like what you're putting
into it rather
than the money and the money will follow. Yeah, so the more you put into being
consistent
during the training, making content, replying to messages, doing your research,
I mean, they're
just some examples of how you can put effort in. Then the more you'll progress
and build
your empire. So thank you for that one, Jay, like that. Yeah, I think that when
you get
to a certain stage, like you said, Sami, you like to focus your goals around
money, but
you've done this for years now and you know, you know, roughly you have a rough
idea of
what you can make and how you do it and stuff like that. So in that instance,
for you that
works, but especially for new people in the beginning, I don't know if it's the
best idea
to focus on the money in the beginning, because one, you're not entirely sure
how much you
could make to your brand new. So, you know, it's always a process to build it
up. So I
think in centering your goals around just actually going online, showing up,
and you
know, putting effort in, like we said, in the training, your profile content,
all that
stuff. If you focus your goals on that, then the money will definitely follow
and then maybe
in the future when you are, you know, more established and you know, you've got
your
regulars and you know that, you know, roughly when I log on, I can usually make
about this
much or whatever else, then yeah, you can think, you know what, I'm going to
put all
this effort and do all of this and I would like to make this much as well today
, then
you can think about that. But yeah, I think in the beginning, maybe not
thinking about
the money because, and because yet you're still new to it and you're still
trying to
just build yourself up on there. I think it's where we feel if you're new, it's
always
best to just go and you speak. When you're new, you're, if you're just
constantly thinking
about the money as well, you're, you don't, you come across as money hungry if
that makes
sense. And I find that my clients don't like that. They want you to be
interested in them.
So I think like once you've learned how like, you know how to be really
interested in them,
then you can, then you can sort of in your head to think about the money. But
if you're
just fully focusing on money, you're not going to be like, how was your day?
Like, Oh, tell
me all about it. Oh, you know, I mean, like, I'm be really interested in them
if that
makes sense. Like, yeah, yeah, because no matter what, go on, go on, don't know
, you
go. I think, I think like, you know, the money manifestations, and talk about
something,
I think they're always good to do. Like it's always good to like your gratitude
for it.
Like it's already happened and like welcome it in and like do those practices.
But I think
we just want to talk about here is like goals, isn't it? Like centering your
goals. If your
goals are like rigid around money, what's better in the beginning to have your
goals
about how many hours you're spending, like honing your craft or updating your
profile
or doing whatever, because four weeks in of like spending only has to be like
five hours
a week, maybe like one hour a night of an evening, like doing these things, you
're going
to see the results after a month. You know, so it takes time to do, doesn't it?
That's another great tip as well, actually, especially if you've had a bit of
time off
like I have over the summer holidays, like being at home with the kids,
refreshing your
profile, I forgot to put that one in. Like I think that makes a massive
difference, like
having a little couple of hours one day where you just spend on really like
going through
your profile and refreshing it and changing it up a little bit. And yeah, that
can be really
helpful.
And one thing I've been doing this week, because I've been getting on, but I've
been like getting
back to it this month is when I log on, I just go and see who's online. And I
just browse
like what the prices are. So kind of prices other people are putting on. I
actually did
it accidentally the first time because I went on in IM, so I changed my prices
for IM and
then I couldn't remember what my normal prices were. So I was like, Oh, I just
have a browse
through and look. But now I've got used to just doing it when I go on. So I
mean, I do
put myself on like the higher end, but I don't go above like really, you know,
far above
what other people are online. Because I think these are more attempts to your
profile, aren't
they?
Yeah.
That's a good practice to go to.
Yes. Okay. Definitely. Okay. Does anybody else have any tips to share about
getting back
into it or getting back to work? Getting back into routine and things. Now that
it's September,
we're all getting back on.
I think one thing that I was going to share as well and is that if like you're
someone
who's like wanting to really give this a go and you know, you've got in your
head, I want
to come like four times a week or five times a week or whatever it is. But at
the minute
you've not been coming at all. Instead of just like throwing yourself in and
like trying
to do like five days a week and five hours each each day or whatever else like
straight
off the bat. Don't do that. Like build yourself up. So I think, you know what
today, I mean,
this week, sorry, I'm going to do two days and I'm going to do two hours each
time and
go on and then just set yourself that like, you know, just start off like with
a small,
small amount and then the week after just up it by a day and up it by an hour
each day
and then same do that for the next few weeks until you're at the point where,
you know,
you're doing the same like the right amount of days and hours that you set
yourself in
the beginning and that way you're just building up to us slowly and it's going
to become a
routine a lot easier than trying to just do it all like, you know, all of a
sudden like
you just now you want to do all these days and hours on cam when you haven't
been doing
that before. I think that's probably a good thing to do. So like, not overwhelm
in yourself
with try to do too much too soon, you know what I mean? Just gradually build up
and then
stay consistent rather than maybe you'll do you'll do the five days, five hours
a day
for the first week or two and then you just won't do anything at all because
you just
crush, you know what I mean? So slowly building it up and then staying
consistent is the most
important thing in this. I went online yesterday, well, it was today your time
but it was yesterday
for me and I hadn't been on it a little while but now after all this time, this
is a different
point now, sorry, but now after all this time I have so many regulars so when I
go on that's
crazy like regulars just even when I was I was not on the front page because I
didn't
have any credits to do so. I always put myself on if I have credits, that's
another point
to always always always do it and especially now that we can't forget to do it
because
we're reminded with the new feature. But I couldn't do it this time, like I
said I had
no credits so I just went on just to see how I how I do and I'm happy with what
I've done
and the time that I've done because I had regulars come through that I've had
for years
and like I said this was another point so it's totally different to the builds
and all
but always ask or always speak about being put on their hot list. This is not
really
a point of getting back into this, it's just a point in general but the more
hot lists
you're on, the better because as soon as your clients go online they say oh
Ruby from my
hot list is online, I'm going to come here so you might not be on the front
page or be
visible to them any other way than just in their hot list. So I think that
makes the
biggest difference on cam as well as being in people's hot lists. You can
actually write
it on your profile at the bottom, I've wrote it online, I've got it in bold
just saying
add me to your hot list just so it's like if they're on my profile and we see
it and
they're like oh yeah I'll add it now like it bakes them like you know give them
an idea
to do it and if I'm if I've got a regular and I'm chatting to them I'll just be
like
babe am I in your hot list yet because you know we want to make sure we can don
't miss
each other in the future blah blah and like normally they'll say oh yeah you're
already
on it or they'll be like I'll put me on now you know what I mean. So yeah that
's a hot
top tip. My chickens have just came out round to say hello to me, I'm just
going to show
you this, oh you can't see.
I'm just going to say hello and give us a little advice but yeah random. But
yeah that's my
one of my top tips because like I said I went on yesterday and I wasn't really
expecting
much and because I'm on quite a lot of hot lists now I've done really well so
yeah hot
lists is in where it at. It makes it easier for getting back to business makes
it easier
for having a brave and coming back doesn't it when you just know where you're
going to
be on.
I think sometimes it's good to have like an accountability buddy as well like
someone
in the group who you can message and be like okay I'm going to do a couple of
days this
week and like not to shame you at all but just to like message each other and
like message
while you're on as well like it's good to have some of the elses also one isn't
it?
Just say you're not so alone in doing it because it can feel quite lonely I
guess when
you're home you're not on your own.
Yeah definitely and you know we just ask one of us like if you don't have
anyone in the
group that you know yet I'm sure out of me Elle and Sammy that one of us are
going to
be online that week so yes you can always message yours and we can keep you
accountable.
And Danny says in the chat in terms of profiles would you ladies suggest having
a selfie as
a profile pick or does it not make much difference?
What would you say ladies?
I'd say yes I would have a selfie but I don't know other people might disagree
I don't know
but yeah I think a selfie does make a difference.
I agree just because when I think of a selfie I think like quite a close up
face which is
always the best for your main picture isn't it like just you in the picture
because obviously
it's a small thumbnail that they only see so they want to be able to see you if
you're
far away they can't see you that well and selfies I think are always good
because you
can even put a filter on it.
I like an Instagram selfie I will put on as my main picture.
They're looking for a connection aren't they so they're looking like I don't
know I always
just think like a nice smiley sort of like face selfie picture does work but I
mean loads
of girls don't do that and they do really well so I don't know I think like a
face I'm
like cleavage like just like this top off of yeah yeah like even like you know
for just
skin it doesn't need to be like full on like boobs out like even if it's just
your skin
on your chest like I think that works really well like my current picture it's
not actually
a selfie when I'm holding the phone like the phone is set up and it's taken
like from the
selfie angle you know what I mean and like Elle said just really close really
cropped
in I've got so many pictures from photoshoots that are like what us that I
think are so
much better than my main picture but they're just so too far away or stuff like
that so
and they actually like the fact that you look real and like a tangible like
person to them
you know what I mean on the photo rather than this like supermodel from a phot
oshoot that's
not real you know what I mean so make a selfie works good in that way because
you look like
a real person that they can actually connect with as well and don't get me
wrong like photos
from photoshoots do well on your profile for like your free gallery or your
private gallery
or the over profile pictures but for the main one I think like a selfie like
definitely definitely
works well yeah and if you need any help Danny on what type of photo you think
would be best
for the main picture because this is actually really important to nail the main
picture because
that's the first thing the client see the main picture and then your profile is
like
super important to nail so if you need any help on what to pick we can all help
you you
can send us options and we can let you know what we think would work best but
yeah a selfie
definitely works and again you can browse if you just click on webcam then
click on online
now you can see who's online and what pictures they've got so you know like
whatever the
else is doing that gives you an idea doesn't it? And one one thing I was just
thinking as
well about like the routine and getting back to business and things I don't
know about
other people but I have ADD so being neuro diverse I think that's one important
point actually
to put on like I have to have my schedule written down so I have like my
monthly I have like
my calendar on my phone and then I've got like a monthly thing but then I've
also got like
my weekly thing which will sets out every day with what I've got that day and
every morning
I look at that list still might forget things now and again but every morning I
look at the
list and I know exactly what I've got that day and I know what times I'm
nowhere I can
look at it and see like where I can fit in any cam or I might have put cam on
there already
and yeah and I think it just that definitely keeps me on track with camming
because sometimes
other things can take priority but if I know if I sit down every morning with
my coffee in the
morning and look at my list for what I've got to the day I know where I can
spot it in
or if something's moved around and they're like oh great it can come there for
an hour so yeah
for people who are neuro diverse like me like having having stuff written down
is really good
and the best planners that I find are like from tk max for like three pounds or
something
and they're so pretty like with all like flowers on and or leopard print or
whatever and they're
so they're so good just give you a daily like rundown of what like little to do
this to check
off and what you're doing that day and stuff so yeah that's a great tip from me
I think that's
definitely something that keeps me on track anyway I write those lists but then
I forget to
look at them because I get too distracted by something else yeah I bought a new
one to start
this year so try in but yeah I can see that elk us um uh ADHD uh so I can't sit
still and I'm fidgeting
um but if you do have any other hints or tips that might help with that it
would be much appreciated
um sorry something that I do is if because I do the same I write a list and
then I'll get distracted
by something else first thing in the morning I'll like whatever you do first
thing like I always
put the kettle on because I like to have a cup of tea so I'll leave like a note
on the on the kettle
or like like under the kettle that says look at your list to remind me to look
at my list and that
works amazing for me and I'm like oh yeah I need to I need to focus today I
need to look at the list
that I spent however long planning yesterday so that's something that I do like
I'll leave it
even like stuff for the kids whatever I'll leave it under their like school bag
like look at look
at the list or remember I don't know whatever it is um so there'll be like
little bits of paper
like scattered around my house under things that I know that I'm going to go to
that remind me
to look to keep on track of something else if that makes sense yeah it does um
that works amazing for
me so give it a try I will go as we know like as scassy as we can be like the
more invested we are
in something and the more we love it the more we're likely to look at it which
is why like the
nicest like things with all it all like just get the nicest little planner
because and yeah I just
do this that's the one thing that I do every single morning I come downstairs I
meet myself a coffee
and sit and look at my list so I think habit is like massive as well isn't it
just habit habit habit
doing it over and over and over so it's like just like second nature then isn't
it yeah but I feel
you it is hard and yeah I think I was in this sometimes but yeah really it's
because I'm also
unmedicated so I'm trying the holistic stuff I was speaking to Sami earlier
about a few health
issues that are not stopping me but just putting a little bit of an obstacle in
the way for me to
be the best version of myself so I can do what I want but I'm trying the
holistic route so if
you anybody's got any hints or tips a bit much appreciated but I've noted them
one down thank you
all right thank you for that Zoe because that's really good that's really yeah
thanks for bringing
that up because that could be a good like you like a little training thing or a
call or something
that we could do about health like managing health and other diagnosis and
stuff alongside
calm because I think that's something that we've not done it's quite important
isn't it so no thanks
I'll have a little think about that um any other questions ladies or if does
anyone want to give
is anyone got like um any other little tips that you want to share?
I would like to ask something else um so you know when you say have you you
come in space
what do people find the feel more comfortable with um because when I've managed
to get on
um I've just been sat on my bed but I'm not comfortable so would it be would
people
advice like to have like a corner with like a chair and a little table or um I
don't know what
people have got for their coming set up so I'll wear everybody else feels most
comfortable
you know one tip one thing that I like and maybe it's not for everyone and it's
not the
most sexy but it is if you don't know what it is pregnancy pillow because you
can like
because it's like like a like that and it just like rests behind your back and
you like sit
into it on your bed for me and have you got one yeah I quite like it because I
just like it can
rest me off like nicely um but I still do get a bit uncomfortable sometimes
when I'm
but um Kelly used to always come at a desk didn't she she's always a desk like
a proper desk on a
chair in front of her um computer and that worked amazing for her so I think it
's whatever works
for you isn't it as long as it's like a nice um like I said like a clean sort
of tidy space
with good lighting I think you can be sitting at a desk or on a bed or
on your sofa wherever you want to be really I think don't you?
I mean I'm sat at my I'm at my gaming desk now on on my on my pc uh what my cat
's are always in here
okay you need to find them they'll go get in trouble
because I've been obviously doing it in the bedroom and leaving my cat's in
front room
but I think I might have to swap it around and put the cats in the bedroom and
and try and come
in here and see how comfortable I am because then I can fit it in my chair yeah
there and they
also if you just sat there and there's not other things that you can do around
you it's really hard
like to just focus and just be pleasant isn't it like you just know like the tv
's there or snacks
or like I can move around and do something else like that I like that a little
bit stuck if I might
just on the bed yeah yeah I think like trying different setups as well like not
just you know
I'll just have them one like you do like have like you said have your one where
your gaming
chair is maybe there's one in the bedroom so you can just try different ones
depends on your mood
you know what I mean so and also just to like switch it up for yourself and
also for your clients
so you're not always just in the same place so you've got like different rooms
for different
moods kinds of things now I've come to my kitchen yesterday and I quite enjoyed
it
I felt like a proper house wifey vibes no kitchens lately so I can put shots on
that
ah that was good lovely thank you no worries
hey ladies hello I think that is probably us for today then isn't it
um thank you so much for coming and thanks again sammy like you know most of
that was your
hard work so thank you so oh well I hope it was helpful yeah it was great and
it'll be available
for people to watch back as well which will be really good I'll let everybody
know about that
when it's up well good luck if anyone's going on tonight I'm ready it's going
on I've got nine
minutes before I can position yeah good luck girlies I love a good night sammy
thank you darling
I'll speak to you soon thank you bye everyone bye